Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 15, 1948; UP056.001.041.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 22, 1948; UP056.001.041.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 29, 1948; UP056.001.041.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 41)
    All Around Club. Alpha Sigma Phi. Fred Althouse elected president of debating society
  - Tufts Weekly, February 26, 1948; UP056.001.041.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1948; UP056.001.041.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1948; UP056.001.041.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1948; UP056.001.041.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1948; UP056.001.041.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1948; UP056.001.041.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 41)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. [Administration] Fall term of 1948, the Administration will combine student fees to cover Infirmary, 3 P's and publications. p. 4. Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 8, 1948; UP056.001.041.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 41)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1948; UP056.001.041.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1948; UP056.001.041.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 41)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] National chapter "adopts" Netherland village of Noordwyck; [Phyllis Ahern [1944]]. Peter Starrett. Jackson graduate was the first Weekly Editor to shed tears on B and M tracks. (includes photo). Alexander Bain Society. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1948; UP056.001.041.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1948; UP056.001.041.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
    Alexander Bain Society. American Institute of Chemical engineers; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, May 27, 1948; UP056.001.041.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 41)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 3, 1948; UP056.001.041.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 41)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1948; UP056.001.042.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 14, 1948; UP056.001.042.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1948; UP056.001.042.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1948; UP056.001.042.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Academic Honors. p. 1 Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1948; UP056.001.042.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Academic Honors. p. 1. Alexander Bain Society. American Institute of Chemical engineers; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, November 11, 1948; UP056.001.042.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    [All Around Club] Presents Marion Keighley Snowden, English lecturer and musician (incl. photo). [All Around Club] Presents Marion Keighley Snowden, English lecturer and musician.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1948; UP056.001.042.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1948; UP056.001.042.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    American institute of electrical engineering; Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1948; UP056.001.042.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Chapter room dedicated to memory of Robert Atlas, killed in action [Alpha Epsilon Pi]; [Administration] View on cuts. p. 1. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Chapter Room dedicated to memory of Robert Atlas, killed in action.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1948; UP056.001.042.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1949; UP056.001.042.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi; Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 20, 1949; UP056.001.042.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 27, 1949; UP056.001.042.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1949; UP056.001.042.00014 (Box 42)
    Carnival Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1949; UP056.001.042.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1949; UP056.001.042.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1949; UP056.001.042.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1949; UP056.001.042.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 31, 1949; UP056.001.042.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1949; UP056.001.042.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1949; UP056.001.042.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1949; UP056.001.042.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1949; UP056.001.042.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1949; UP056.001.042.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 42)
    Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1949; UP056.001.042.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 42)
  - Tufts Weekly, Freshmen Edition, 1949; UP056.001.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 29, 1949; UP056.001.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1949; UP056.001.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 14, 1949; UP056.001.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1949; UP056.001.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1949; UP056.001.043.00006 (Box 43)
    Academic Honors. p. 1. [Alexander, Frank] Walter Dow, Tufts athletes are attended to by popular trainer (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1949; UP056.001.043.00007 (Box 43)
    Academic Honors. pp. 1, 8. Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1949; UP056.001.043.00008 (Box 43)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Omega. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1949; UP056.001.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 1, 1949; UP056.001.043.00010 (Box 43)
    [Alumni council] Approves plan for Tufts College Radio station with call letters WGI
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1949; UP056.001.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1949; UP056.001.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 12, 1950; UP056.001.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 19, 1950; UP056.001.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 16, 1950; UP056.001.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 23, 1950; UP056.001.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 2, 1950; UP056.001.043.00017 (Box 43)
    All Around Club. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 9, 1950; UP056.001.043.00018 (Box 43)
    All Around Club; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, March 16, 1950; UP056.001.043.00019 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 23, 1950; UP056.001.043.00020 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 30, 1950; UP056.001.043.00021 (Box 43)
    [American association of University professors] Tufts chapter discusses honor system
  - Tufts Weekly, April 13, 1950; UP056.001.043.00022 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 20, 1950; UP056.001.043.00023 (Box 43)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 27, 1950; UP056.001.043.00024 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 4, 1950; UP056.001.043.00025 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 11, 1950; UP056.001.043.00026 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 18, 1950; UP056.001.043.00027 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 25, 1950; UP056.001.043.00028 (Box 43)
  - Tufts Weekly, Freshmen Edition, 1950; UP056.001.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 28, 1950; UP056.001.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1950; UP056.001.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 12, 1950; UP056.001.044.00004 (Box 44)
    Alpha Sigma Phi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1950; UP056.001.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1950; UP056.001.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1950; UP056.001.044.00007 (Box 44)
    Academic Honors. p. 1 Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1950; UP056.001.044.00008 (Box 44)
    Alpha Tau Omega; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, November 16, 1950; UP056.001.044.00009 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 30, 1950; UP056.001.044.00010 (Box 44)
    [Alumni council] Goal of $1,000,000 for Tufts centennial fund
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1950; UP056.001.044.00011 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1950; UP056.001.044.00012 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 21, 1950; UP056.001.044.00013 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 11, 1951; UP056.001.044.00014 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 18, 1951; UP056.001.044.00015 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1951; UP056.001.044.00016 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 22, 1951; UP056.001.044.00017 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1951; UP056.001.044.00018 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1951; UP056.001.044.00019 (Box 44)
    Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1951; UP056.001.044.00020 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1951; UP056.001.044.00021 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 29, 1951; UP056.001.044.00022 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1951; UP056.001.044.00023 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 19, 1951; UP056.001.044.00024 (Box 44)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Blood donations to Veterans Hospital.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1951; UP056.001.044.00025 (Box 44)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. American Institute of Chemical engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1951; UP056.001.044.00026 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1951; UP056.001.044.00027 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1951; UP056.001.044.00028 (Box 44)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 13, 1951; UP056.001.045.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1951; UP056.001.045.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1951; UP056.001.045.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1951; UP056.001.045.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1951; UP056.001.045.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
    [Alexander, Frank] Joe Standel. Sports trainer (incl. photo)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1951; UP056.001.045.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1951; UP056.001.045.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
    Academic Honors; pp.1,8.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1951; UP056.001.045.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 29, 1951; UP056.001.045.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1951; UP056.001.045.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 13, 1951; UP056.001.045.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1952; UP056.001.045.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1952; UP056.001.045.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1952; UP056.001.045.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 28, 1952; UP056.001.045.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 6, 1952; UP056.001.045.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 13, 1952; UP056.001.045.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1952; UP056.001.045.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 27, 1952; UP056.001.045.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 9, 1952; UP056.001.045.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1952; UP056.001.045.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 17, 1952; UP056.001.045.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 25, 1952; UP056.001.045.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1952; UP056.001.045.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
    All around club; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, May 8, 1952; UP056.001.045.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1952; UP056.001.045.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 45)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 18, 1952; UP056.001.046.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 2, 1952; UP056.001.046.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1952; UP056.001.046.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Admissions, 1952] [Grant Curtis] Admissions Procedure Has Become Complex; Alumni famous for contribution to Industry, Science, Math, and Music: Vannevar Bush, Amos E. Dolbear, Robert Rounseville, Norbert Weinter, p4
  - Tufts Weekly, October 16, 1952; UP056.001.046.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    Alpha Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 23, 1952; UP056.001.046.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 30, 1952; UP056.001.046.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 6, 1952; UP056.001.046.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    Academic Honors; pp. 1,8.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 13, 1952; UP056.001.046.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 20, 1952; UP056.001.046.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Purchase house at 6-8 Capen St. [incl. photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, December 4, 1952; UP056.001.046.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 11, 1952; UP056.001.046.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Administration] Fines for vacation cuts: signing off-signing on discontinued. p. 1. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Activities and Officers.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 18, 1952; UP056.001.046.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 8, 1953; UP056.001.046.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 15, 1953; UP056.001.046.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 19, 1953; UP056.001.046.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1953; UP056.001.046.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 5, 1953; UP056.001.046.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Help Week. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 12, 1953; UP056.001.046.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 19, 1953; UP056.001.046.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Reginald H. Alleyne Jr. (1954) Elected track captain for 1953-54 (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, March 26, 1953; UP056.001.046.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - The Harvard Crimson [The Tufts Weekly April Fools' Day Edition], April 1, 1953; UP056.001.046.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 2, 1953; UP056.001.046.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 16, 1953; UP056.001.046.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1953; UP056.001.046.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Reggie Alleyne and Bob Jones, 1953-04-24; UP056.001.046.00024.00001 (Box 46)
    Caption:The finals in the 100-yard dash show a close finish with Reggie Alleyne (far left) the winner. Bob Jones (center) takes second. Joe Pezzo of RI is third and Roger Schuler of Tufts took Fourth.
    Track (Men's); Athletics; Black students; Students; Alleyne, Reginald; Jones, Robert; Tufts University
  - Tufts Weekly, April 30, 1953; UP056.001.046.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 7, 1953; UP056.001.046.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Activities and Officers.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 14, 1953; UP056.001.046.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 46)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 21, 1953; UP056.001.046.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 46)
    Content Warning
    This newspaper issue contains an article which depicts and describes minstrelsy and blackface. The article is located on the last page of the issue, on the upper left side and contains an image of the cast in blackface. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 18, 1953; UP056.001.047.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1953; UP056.001.047.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alumnae Hall] to be built on Talbot Avenue
  - Tufts Weekly, October 8, 1953; UP056.001.047.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 16, 1953; UP056.001.047.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 22, 1953; UP056.001.047.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 47)
    James L. Adams. Russell Lecture, 1953
  - Tufts Weekly, October 29, 1953; UP056.001.047.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 5, 1953; UP056.001.047.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    Academic Honors; pp. 1, 5, 8. [Albu, Austen] Labor member of Parliament is University Lecturer, 1953.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1953; UP056.001.047.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Albu, Austen] Labor member of Parliament is University Lecturer, 1953.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1953; UP056.001.047.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alumnae Hall] to be built on Talbot Avenue, groundbreaking
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1953; UP056.001.047.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1953; UP056.001.047.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1953; UP056.001.047.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1954; UP056.001.047.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1954; UP056.001.047.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 26, 1954; UP056.001.047.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1954; UP056.001.047.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1954; UP056.001.047.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Reginald H. Alleyne Jr. (A54) Sees Sports Part of Rounded Growth (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1954; UP056.001.047.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alexander, Frank] Mark Needle. Personality sketch (incl. photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1954; UP056.001.047.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1954; UP056.001.047.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Administration] Faculty modifies grading plan. p. 7. Alpha Sigma Phi; Alpha Xi Delta
  - Tufts Weekly, April 15, 1954; UP056.001.047.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
    [Alpha Xi Delta] Sponsors dutch pianist; [Administration] Administrative Committee. New policy concerning transfer of summer school credits. p. 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 22, 1954; UP056.001.047.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1954; UP056.001.047.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1954; UP056.001.047.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1954; UP056.001.047.00025 (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1954; UP056.001.047.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 47)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 16, 1954; UP056.001.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 30, 1954; UP056.001.048.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
    Death of (9/19/1954) Frank Alexander; [Alumnae Hall] to be completed in Spring 1955]
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1954; UP056.001.048.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 15, 1954; UP056.001.048.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1954; UP056.001.048.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1954; UP056.001.048.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1954; UP056.001.048.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
    Academic Honors; P.1.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1954; UP056.001.048.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
    .
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1954; UP056.001.048.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1954; UP056.001.048.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1954; UP056.001.048.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1954; UP056.001.048.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1955; UP056.001.048.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1955; UP056.001.048.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25, 1955; UP056.001.048.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
    [Administration] Personality sketches of staff members: Jean Prentiss and Mildred Coolidge. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1955; UP056.001.048.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
    Alpha Xi Delta; [Administration] Personality sketches of staff members: Jean Prentiss and Mildred Coolidge. p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1955; UP056.001.048.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1955; UP056.001.048.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1955; UP056.001.048.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1955; UP056.001.048.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 48)
    [Administration] Considers cut policy. pp. 1, 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 22, 1955; UP056.001.048.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1955; UP056.001.048.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1955; UP056.001.048.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1955; UP056.001.048.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 48)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1955; UP056.001.048.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 48)
    [Alumnae Hall] cornerstone laid; American Institute of Chemical engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, September 15, 1955; UP056.001.049.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 30, 1955; UP056.001.049.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1955; UP056.001.049.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 49)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 14, 1955; UP056.001.049.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 49)
    All Around Club. American Institute of Chemical engineers